原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
翻译     哈里不是波特  易碎的绝对  菜一
翻译     克里斯  DerbyNinja  江夏
翻译     omiyask617  小黄鱼  苏葵
校对     苏葵
时间轴     Jenny  DA
后期     渔夫
总监     苏葵
废话  废话  废话  废话...
Blah, blah, blah, blah, blah...
我从没见过有人把自己的智商写到简历里呢
I've never seen anyone put their IQ on a CV before.
你面过多少家了
How many of these have you had?
九个  四个在纽约
Nine. Four in New York,
四个在这边  一次网面
four here, and a Skype.
那你还来这干什么
Why are you here, then?
我的回答可能比较直接  但...
Well, it's not a very political answer, but...
我认为那些找私人家教的家长
I think mediocrity is too well-hidden
把平庸之才都精心掩盖起来了
by parents who hire private tutors.
而我是靠自己来的
I am here on my own.
我希望把自己的观点讲清楚
I want to be able to explain myself clearly,
并且让大家对我的想法持接受的态度
urn, and have people be receptive to my ideas.
你就是靠这个来获得认可的吗
Is that how you get your validation?
让大家都倾听你的话
People listening to you?
相对于什么呢...
As opposed to, uh...?
每个成功的企业中
Every successful business
都有很多人花钱去
is full of people who've spent money
培养原本平庸的能力
nurturing unremarkable talent.
你为什么要读地理
Why did you read Geography?
前一年申请读地理的人最少
Geography had the least amount of applicants the year before.
这就是个边际收益的边际博弈
You know, it's a marginal game about marginal gains.
走个捷径也没什么错
Nothing wrong with the back door.
相比起耶稣基督和玛格丽特·撒切尔
I played third fiddle to two figures in my mother's life,
对我妈来说我是无足轻重的第三个
Jesus Christ and Margaret Thatcher.
那你对他们二位的看法呢
And where do you stand on them?
一人是我们大家在这的原因  另一人是个木匠
One's the reason we're all here, and the other's a carpenter.
我认为这是最接近以才取人的地方了
I think this is the closest thing to a meritocracy there is.
而我就希望别人
And I only ever want to be judged
能以我的能力来评判我
on the strength of my abilities.
并付你相应的薪水
And paid for it.
应该是吧
I guess.
我没想到我们还从
I didn't realize that we recruited
纽约州立大学宾汉姆顿分校招聘
from SUNY Binghamton.
应该不在目标学校里的
It's a nontarget.
你能给我们讲个笑话吗
Can you tell us a joke?
好
Uh, ye-- yeah.
是有点和工作之类的相关的
it's a bit for work, urn, or whatever.
你知道要把你彻底弄来伦敦
You know how many mountains I'd have to move
我得要搞定多少个障碍吗
to get you to London for good?
Industry
投行风云
第一季  第一集
你好像不太知道怎么玩转那个吧
You don't look sure how to navigate that.
请今年的毕业生们到二楼礼堂集合
Would this year's graduate class please assemble
参加你们第三周的就职活动
in the second-floor auditorium for your week-three induction.
准备好被洗脑了吗
You ready to be indoctrinated?
楼下见吧
See you down there.
真的不用我给您带点什么吗
Sure I can't get you anything?
罗伯特
Uh, yeah, Robert,
实际上我一直都想问问你
I've been meaning to ask, actually.
你家里有亲人去世了吗
Urn, did someone very close to you die?
这西装颜色真黑啊
It's a very dark suit.
请节哀  但你还把...
I'm sorry for your loss, but have you left the, uh,
商标留在袖子上了  好家伙
label on your sleeve there as well? Wow!
对  是新的
Yeah, it's new.
你看着就像个本地夜店里的保安
Yeah, you look like regional nightclub security.
只接待男士的店的保安
Stag do security.
这样吧  让我来...
Actually, let me just--
让我来帮你吧
Let me just do that for you,
省得你在同伴面前被嘲笑
before you embarrass yourself in front of your peers.
要知道  你这么做无异于树了个大广告牌
You see, what you've done there is actually erect a billboard
-告诉人家你有多嫩  -好吧  有意思
- to how gauche you are. - Yeah, nice one.
女士们先生们  罗伯特穿的是泰德·贝克
Robert wears Ted Baker, ladies and gentlemen!
大家周知一下
Just so you know!
-我觉得你挺精神的  -谢谢
- I think you look great. - Thanks.
世界摔角娱乐WWE九十年代末辉煌时期的著名选手
《恶劣态度时代》里的送葬者
The Undertaker, Attitude Era!
电梯门开
Doors opening.
皮尔庞特公司
我想我们在酒会上见过
Urn, I think we met at the drinks?
我想你搞错了
I don't think that was me.
好吧
Okay.
没关系  免费酒吧
It's cool. Free bar.
我是外汇销售部的雅思敏
I'm Yasmin from FX sales.
我们好像在同一层工作
I think we work on the same floor.
哈珀  消费者投资组合服务团队
Harper, CPS team.
他在我们队工作  是个花美男
He works on my team. He's a whole snacc.
如果你喜欢这一款  算是吧
If you're into that kinda thing, I guess.
欢迎  毕业生们
Welcome, graduates.
人是我们的资本
年轻人是我们的资本
Young people are our capital.
毕业生是我们的资本
Graduates are our capital.
虽然我很荣幸恭喜你们
And while it's my pleasure to congratulate you
获得这份实习
on this placement,
为了留下  你们要从现在就开始努力
the work to stay here starts now.
哪位高管为你担保
Which senior vouches for you,
你给客户留下的印象
the impression that you make on clients,
都将被评估
will all be evaluated.
六个月之后  在裁员日
In six months' time, on RIF day--
也就是削减人力的意思  你们将站在这个房间
that's Reduction in Force -- you'll be standing in this room,
告诉我们所有人
telling all of us...
你为什么值得被长期雇用
why you should be hired permanently to your desk.
皮尔庞特是世界上
Pierpoint is the world's
最杰出的金融服务机构
preeminent financial services institution.
我们期望你能表现得像休戚与共的一份子
We expect you to behave like you have a stake in it.
像主人翁一样行动  让客户富裕  让我们富裕
Act like an owner. Enrich your clients, enrich us,
让自己富裕
enrich yourselves.
看看坐在你旁边的男孩女孩吧
So, look at the guy or gal next to you.
仔细看看  你觉得你比他们强吗
Really look. Do you think you're better than them?
也许你是
Maybe you are.
但再过六个月  将有半数人被淘汰
But half of you won't be here in six months.
努力证明自己不可或缺吧
Just make yourselves indispensable.
特浓柴茶加一勺乳清
Extra dirty chai with a scoop of whey.
脱脂拿铁
Skinny latte.
...不管他叫你做什么
...whatever he tells you to do.
你有什么想让我查查看的吗
Is there anything you want looking at?
我们当时在他的双体船上
We were on his catamaran,
然后向导抓住一条石斑鱼
and then the guide caught some grouper
在船的另一边直接炸了
and fried it on the side of the boat.
棒极了
Yeah, it was beautiful.
找瑞西要一年期五十万基点美元值的
Hey, ask Rishi for the level of one year, one year, euro swap
欧元汇率
in 500k DV01.
-瑞西  -今天就要
- Rishi. - Today, please.
瑞西
Rishi?
-你能发一份...  -放松
- Can you send-- - Relax.
这不是拍卖行
It's not an auction house.
我刚把我算的发给你了  在你的工作账户上了
I've just sent out my runs. They're on your Bloomie.
你可以坐下了
You can sit down now.
我刚才在跟芬马什的费利姆通电话
I was talking to Felim at Fenmarsh.
他很满意你帮他处理的美国尾部风险工作
He's impressed with that US tail risk work you did for him.
他给我发了一封邮件表示感谢
He sent me an email to say thanks.
抱歉  我不想堵住你的邮箱
Sorry, I didn't want to clog your inbox.
不用抱歉  记住在这要努力给自己争功
Don't apologize. Just remember to talk your book here,
否则大家会忽视的
or people will miss it.
我们想让你尽快在能签下单子
We want to get you printing business as soon as possible.
哈珀  哈珀
Oh, Harper. Harper.
抱歉  等我喘口气
Sorry, just catch my breath.
-没问题  -循环一下
- Sure. - Cycled in.
好了  我还没拿到你的大学成绩单
Yes, uh, I still don't have your university transcript.
真的很抱歉  我会尽快处理的
I'm really sorry. I will get on it.
上周你就这么说的
You said that last week.
哈珀·斯登  你是国际候选人  是吧
Oh, Harper Stern, you're an international candidate, right?
我这还没有你的成绩单
I'm still missing your transcript.
我还在等我的学校寄过来
I'm still waiting on my college to send a copy.
他们出了名的慢
They are notoriously slow.
我们现在就捅破这层窗户纸吧
We're moving out of that gray area now,
这已经对我们构成了小小的困扰
where it's becoming a bit of a problem for us,
对你来说也是问题
and therefore a problem for you.
抱歉  你可以继续你的事了
Sorry. You may continue your quest.
去厕所吧
For the loo.
谢谢
Thank you.
不要觉得奇怪  我有事找你帮忙
哈珀
Harper.
你回过家吗
Have you been home?
你好像没回过家
You're just, like, never in your room,
还穿着和昨天一样的衣服
and you're wearing an... identical outfit to yesterday?
我要记下晚上工作的时间
Well, I'm logging those nocturnal hours.
尽量给公司留下一个好印象
Trying to make a good impression, you know?
不用估算
Don't try to figure out
投资银行部一小时会付你多少钱
how much you get paid by the hour in IBD,
因为我向你保证肯定会比最低工资还要少
because I will guarantee you it is less than minimum wage.
在我看来  我在象牙塔的上端
Well, the way I see it, I'm in the ivory tower upstairs,
而你和农民们一起躺在地板上
you're down here on the floor with the peasants.
有这么一瞬间  我以为你会找我攀谈
Well, for a minute, I thought you were actually gonna talk.
你来这里已经三个星期
You know, you've been here for three weeks,
却几乎没和我说过一句话
and you've barely said a word to me.
抱歉  我只是一直忙着
I'm sorry. I've just been underwater
备份埃里克的账户
backing up Eric's accounts.
我知道我们俩都是埃里克的手下
I know we both work for Eric,
但我是你的部门经理
but I'm your line manager.
他有叫你去见客户吗
Has he asked you to meet clients?
当然没有
No. For sure not, no.
明天我和马隆默瑟公司的人一起吃晚饭
Well, I've got this dinner tomorrow night with Mallon Mercer.
妮可·克雷格  虽然只是我单方面邀约
Nicole Craig. It's a bit of a one-way relationship,
但是对公司来说很重要
but substantial to the firm.
这是一个提高你作为毕业生知名度的机会
It's a chance to increase your visibility as a grad.
你要一起去吗
Do you want to tag along?
好的
Yeah. Yes.
我会查查她的资历
I'll look into her mandate.
不用想太多
Don't overthink it.
你有这么渴吗
Are you that thirsty?
如果你有三十块的饭补
Well, you know, if you got a 30 quid meal allowance,
为什么不用光呢
like, why would you not use all of it?
太没品位了
That's very naff.
你的模型怎么样了
How's your model?
我会在早上做完的
I'll finish it in the morning.
发给我  我能做
Send it over my way, I've got capacity.
你怎么做得了
How do you have capacity?
-耐抗的金融人对吧  -我不知道那是什么
- Brutal finance guy, innit? - I don't know what that is.
你要走了
You bouncing'?
现在才10点15分
Hey, man. Hey. It's only 10: 15.
这里没人会这么和你说
No one here is actually gonna tell you this,
但是你要坐在办公室里
but you need to put in face time.
其实我不用
Actually, I don't.
熬夜并不能提高我的工作效率
Staying up all night doesn't enhance my work.
伙计  伙计
Mate. Mate!
评估报告  管理案例
-给我看看你的房间  -我的房间
- Let me see your room. - My room?
-好  -看吧
- Yeah. - Yeah, check it.
皮尔庞特的临时住所
It's Pierpoint's temp accommodation
-给外地人住的  -好吧
- for out-of-towners. - Okay, okay, okay.
看起来不错
Looks crazy.
让那些常青藤盟校的黑鬼
How easy is it to get them Ivy League niggas
和你一起回家容易吗
to come home with you?
我只是来工作的
I'm just here to work.
只有和你一起的时候才会涉及到性
It's only with you that everything becomes sexual.
所以你打电话给我
So the only reason you're calling me
只是因为你想要一张假成绩单吗
is that you want a fake transcript?
你肯定非常需要
You must need it pretty bad.
你确定你只想要张假成绩单吗
You sure that's all you need?
怎么  我还需要别的东西吗
Why? What else would I want?
你拿什么来交换
What are you offering?
你找到工作了吗  陶德
Did you get a job yet, Todd?
没有  干了些活  还没收到钱
Nah, I did some unpaid shit.
通过兴趣来赚钱太难了
It's hard to make money off your passion.
除非你的兴趣就是赚钱
You know, unless your passion's... money.
去你的
Fuck you.
好吧  但如果我能让你们银行
Okay, but if I can make your bank
相信你是研究生毕业  对你有多大价值
think you're graduated, what's that worth to you?
干嘛  你今晚缺个炮友  是吗
What, you didn't get to fuck tonight? Is that it?
我是说...  *如果你需要大屌*
I mean...*If you need dick*
*就来找我吧*
*I got you*
屁股翘起来  美臀给我看看
Ass up. What that ass do?
你没听老爹的话  他会...
You don't listen to what Daddy says. He's going to--
别管他
Just ignore it.
哥们  早会要开始了
This morning meeting's about to start, mate.
如果老爹的话真对你有影响
If-- if what Daddy said actually affected you,
你就不会还在打电话了
then you wouldn't still be on the phone now.
你为什么修改加权平均资本成本
Why have you changed the WACC?
贴现现金流估值太低了
The DCF was coming out too low.
那和可比交易估值相比呢
Well, how does it compare to the transaction comps?
这些盈利前独角兽企业交易都是疯狂翻倍
These pre-profit unicorns trade on crazy multiples.
八倍  九倍
Eight times, nine times.
加上流动性贴水  我们才刚超过贴现现金流估值
Less a liquidity discount, We'd be just over the DCF.
好的  很棒
All right, fantastic.
这是什么
What's that?
这是我的模型
That's my model.
你为什么在建模  加斯才负责建模
Why are you doing the model? Gus is doing the model.
我有余力  我只是想超前一点
I had capacity. I just wanted to get ahead.
哈里  我叫你做项目分析报告
Hari, I told you to do the pitchbook,
你他妈就去做项目分析报告  好吗
so do the fucking pitchbook, okay?
饥饿救星想要提升配送速度
HungerFix want to optimize delivery speed,
所以他们在寻找有优秀导航技术的中型企业
so they're looking at mid-caps with best-in-class GPS tech.
背景清楚的公司  户户送  优步美食...
Clear comps. Deliveroo, Uber Eats...
我找到一些公司  有很好的卫星导航专利
I've found something with good sat-nav IP.
-他们体量很小  -别他妈找了
- They're quite small-- - Don't fucking fish!
严格按流程办
Stick to the formatting.
还有  记住了  要用12号的瑞士风格字体
And for fuck sake, make sure the font's Helvetica 12
不然董事总经理会发火的
or the MD will freak.
而且我可能得带你们中的一个去会场
And I might have to take one of you into the pitch.
我会主导  但你们出现一下也挺好
I'll lead, but it'll be good for your visibility.
-你什么在做我的模型  -哥们  这是团队工作
- Why are you doing my model? - Mate, it's the team's work.
不  这是我的工作
No, it's my work.
你总觉得要一直比出胜负  那不是我的错
It's not my fault you feel the need to keep score.
我就不这样
I don't.
所以  我猜昨晚是在博伊斯代尔餐厅
So, I'm guessing last night was Boisdale?
博伊斯代尔  赫特福德五号  还有不变的安娜贝尔
Boisdale. Five Hertford, and then, inevitably, Annabel's.
三巨头
The triumvirate.
就像老朋友的拥抱
Like the embrace of an old friend.
对了  好吧  我发表了一篇文章
Right. Okay, urn... So, I've published a piece
回顾金融危机后的这十年
looking back at the decade post-crisis.
三段式  住房  2007至2009年...
Three stages. Housing, 2007 to 2009--
我们怎么才能把后视镜里的东西变成钱呢
How are we supposed to monetize what's in the rear-view mirror?
好吧...
Well, urn...
有新的买入建议吗
Any new buy recommendations?
还是强烈推荐美国方面
Still overweight with a preference for the US.
即使保证金和估值一直居高不下吗
Even with margins and valuations at all-time highs?
如果没有实质变化  为什么要费心发表呢
Why bother publishing if there are no material changes?
好吧  我想卡斯帕会为我的性格买单的
Well, I suppose Kaspar can pay for my personality.
你不介意的话可以把我的笔记读给他听
Well, you can read my note out loud to him if you'd like.
这又不是广告  对吧
It's not exactly commercial, is it?
研究团队再一次出色地
Once again, the research team excel
浪费了销售团队的时间
in wasting salespeople's time.
又一次退场了
Oh, another walkout.
一份鳕鱼配培根  不要奶酪
So, it's one cob with bacon, no Stilton,
另一份不要...  不不  等等  抱歉
and the other one without-- No, no, no, Wait. Sorry.
第一份是要培根的  谢谢  还有...
The first one I need with bacon. Urn, thank you. And, uh-- Oh.
抱歉  我特别说了不要沙拉酱
Sorry, I specifically said, "No dressing."
你又把牛给喂饱了吗
Keeping the cattle fed and watered?
我的第一顿正经晚餐是跟菲利普·贾布里一起吃的
My first proper dinner was with Philippe Jabre.
就是对冲基金的那个人  他很有名
You know, from hedge funds? He's famous.
松久信幸  他被誉为餐饮界的艺术家
我们十几个人在松久餐厅  08年前的松久
Dozen of us at Nobu, pre-08 Nobu.
我有肠胃炎
I had gastroenteritis.
当场吐了出来
Threw up at the table.
贾布里说那是整晚我嘴里冒出的
Jabre said it was the first interesting thing
第一件有趣的事
to come out of my mouth all night.
那只说对了一半
That's only half true.
但他还是给我打了电话
But he still called.
我依然拿到了他的单子
I still printed his business.
那才最重要
That's the bar.
别听达莉娅说这只是次晚餐
Don't let Daria tell you it's just dinner.
我会好好策划的
I'll work on a pitch.
你又要逼哪个毕业生
Which grad do you have to bully
去替你买三明治
to get a fucking sanger?
费利姆  卡普里怎么样了
Felim, how was Capri?
-你必须离开这里  -为什么
- You need to get out of here. - Why?
过去48小时内你只离开了一次这幢楼
You've only left the building once in the last 48 hours.
你的身份识别卡已被自动标记为红色
It's automatically red flagged by your ID card.
我不想知道你前几天是在哪里睡的
I don't want to know where you've been sleeping,
但我需要你从视觉上离开这间办公室
but optically, I need you to walk out of the office,
刷卡出去  做点什么  然后再回来
tap your card out, do whatever, then come back.
-不许再被标红了  -好的  对不起
- No more red flag. - Okay. Sorry.
你没惹麻烦
You're not in trouble.
我很感激你想公司之所想  急公司之所急
I appreciate how you're meeting the needs of the business.
谢谢
Thanks.
把这些水扔了  好吗
Get rid of the fucking water, yeah?
别太过分了
And don't take the piss.
去喝一杯吧
Go grab a pint.
工作结束后我可能会去找你
I might come find you when the work's done.
永远没个消停
No rest for the wicked.
有权势的女性
Women of power
似乎不喜欢给后来的女性机会
seem to like to withhold sunlight from women coming up.
2020金融女性论坛  马隆默瑟公司妮可·克雷格
这不对  我们不能这样做
It's not cool. We can't be doing that.
成功
The success...
你有点受虐狂
You're a bit of a masochist.
-你说什么  -在会议上怼克莱门特
- Excuse me? - Negging Clement in the meeting.
我花了几个月才写出
I spent months writing something
那些销售在电话中重复的统一话术
for the fucking salesmen to parrot over the phone,
克莱门特都不愿意连屈尊
and Clement doesn't even have the humility to listen
听五分钟
for five fucking minutes.
对  但这是他的项目
Yeah, but his war stories though.
他就是个怪胎
He's a fucking dinosaur.
他花了两年才学会对我说"早上好"
It took two years for him to say "Good morning" to me.
他永远不会跟你说话的
He's never going to speak to you.
知道了  好吧  伙计  随便吧
Yeah, all right, mate. Whatever.
我的意思是  别指望
I'm just saying, don't think
那种家伙会在公司裁员时保护你
that a guy like that's gonna protect you on RIF.
克莱门特  他有卡斯帕的支持  那是个大客户
Clement, he's-- he's got Kaspar, that's one fucking account,
的确  这是个大客户
and yeah, it's-- it's big,
但确保你能活下来的唯一方法是大声说
but the only way to guarantee you survive is to say,
"我是创始人  我有笔新买卖"
"I am an originator. I won new business."
我记得当时我和阿德里安在一起
I remember I was with, um, Adrian.
我这脑子  那地方叫什么来着
Come on, what did this place used to be called?
拜托  那地方曾有个
It's, uh, come on, it used to have
很糟糕的两个字的名字
some really awful single syllable name
好像叫"特技"之类的
like "Stunt," or something like that.
看起来就像个建筑工地
Looked like a fucking building site.
所以  她有  她有"开机"按钮吗
So, um, does she have a-- does she have an "ON" button?
我一直在研究
Uh, I was looking into
-你所从事的买卖  -好吧  当务之急
- the business you did with... - Right. Uh, priorities.
我们可以点一些
Shall we get some wine
喝起来不像涂料稀释剂的酒吗
that doesn't taste like paint thinner?
-当然他妈的没问题  -是的
- Abso-fucking-lutely. - Yeah.
好吧  有些什么酒呢
Okay, what do we have?
你认识加斯吗
Do you, uh, do you know Gus?
是的  我们是室友  大学时就是了
Uh, yeah, yeah, I live with him. I lived with him at uni.
他上大学后我们就没怎么联系了
Oh, uh, we sort of lost touch while he was there.
我以前跟他一个学校的  跟他们都是
I went to school with him. With all those guys.
没想到你忍了这么久才提起伊顿
Surprised it took you that long to mention Eton.
"比他高两个年级  是个团长"  他如是说道
"Two years above. House Captain," He said.
我知道你们俩的很多事情
I know a lot about you two.
这样啊
Yeah.
回头见
Catch you later.
不停地说"一切都会好的"
Saying "Everything's gonna be okay" over and over
也阻止不了房子着火坍塌  不是吗
doesn't stop your house burning down around you, does it?
最终我们都得吃掉自己的宠物
Eventually we shall be eating our pets.
如果这是你的人生哲学  你可以推销它
Well, if that's your philosophy, you could trade it.
非常合理的两倍价
Extremely reasonable at twice the price.
我在反讽  这个价格非常昂贵
I'm being sarcastic. It is reassuringly expensive.
以4%收益率买入美国十年国债期权
Buy an option on the US ten year at four percent.
你还没出生前
Yields haven't been there
就没什么收益率了
since before you were born.
事实上是两千年初的时候
Actually, since the early aughts.
你那时还只有屁大点吧
Were you even sentient then?
不好意思  妮可  新人一般不负责给建议
Sorry, Nicole, graduates don't normally pitch.
谁管那么多  让她讲
Fuck that, let her talk.
如今总统败坏了
With the president bulldozing the reputation
美国在海外的名声
of the US overseas, you know,
我个人认为
for me, it follows that...
这个政府将完全抹杀财政部的信誉
the administration will totally kill the rep of treasuries.
而且和中国对着干也没好处
And pissing in China's mouth isn't gonna help.
没错  依我所见
Exactly. Personally?
我们迟早会经历一场大型做空
I just think we're due an enormous selloff.
我们在低调地和所有的
We're low key throwing ourselves in cold wars
贸易伙伴打冷战
with all of our trading partners.
中国是全球最大的美元持有者
China are the biggest global holder of US paper.
如果他们开始抛售美元  收益率很快会超过4%
If they start dumping, yields will soar past four percent.
如果你觉得房子要烧毁了
If you think the house is burning down,
你就这样从中获利
this is how you monetize it.
通常来说  在这个市场里做空会亏损
Bearish people lose money in this market.
没错  但是现在世界盛行尾部风险
Yeah, but the world's pregnant with tail risk.
没错  这是最后的赌局
Right, and this is a play for the end.
你们要再喝点什么吗
Who wants another drink, anyone?
我的物理治疗师最看不惯我宿醉
My PT hates it when I'm hungover.
我们恐怕必须带着爱意离开你了
We are gonna have to love you and leave you, I'm afraid.
-尽管很困难  -好吧  我就不起身了
- As hard as that is. - Right, well, I won't get up.
你可以滚去睡觉了
Fine for you to piss off to bed,
但我想听哈珀把话说完  行吗
but I'll let Harper finish her thoughts, yeah?
好吧
Right.
妮可
Nicole.
哈珀  记得付账
Harper. Pick up the bill.
米奇  你明早应该清醒一些
Mikey, you should be fresh in the morning.
没错  我会做节制一点的那个人
Yeah, I'll be the responsible one.
这是我的卡
Uh, here is my card.
谢谢
Thank you.
我可以发一封邮件给你
So, I can write up an email...
我不觉得你是个销售
I don't think you're a saleswoman.
我在夸奖你
That's a compliment.
销售卖的是肯定性
Salespeople sell... certainty.
很好
Ah, lovely.
生活多美好
What a life.
我叫了一辆优步
Got us an Uber.
这个时段溢价两倍
There's two times surge.
你花两倍的价钱回家
You pay twice as much to go home
却只有一半的快乐
and have half the fun.
擦一擦你的鼻子吧
Wipe your fucking nose.
两品脱就把你放倒了  对吧
It only takes two pints, doesn't it?
所有外展的家伙都抱团  我就知道
All the Outreach guys together, of course.
-这是因为...  -多样性雇员  我知道
- It's a scheme for... - Diversity hires, I know.
加斯觉得他看不上那些
Gus thinks he's above all that.
-我真讨厌你的友情  -那好  你出局了
- I resent your friendship. - Good. You're staying out.
好吧  我也不想被当成你们俩的朋友
Yeah, I'm not sure I can be seen fraternizing with you two.
我可一点没喝醉
I'm sober as a judge.
-进车里去  伙计  回家吧  -别推我
- Get in the car, man. Go home. - Don't push me.
尽量别吐在车里
Try not to throw up in there.
好的  老兄  去皮尔庞特
Yeah, mate, Pierpoint.
拜托带他回家  地址已经写进去了
Take him home, please. Destination's in.
明早我可以把期权提议发给你
I can write up that option idea for you in the morning.
如果你想的话
If you want.
好
Okay.
我能靠近点吗
Can I come a bit closer?
我太累了
I'm so tired.
他能把你送到任何地方
He can drop you anywhere.
萨瑟克
S-Southwark.
不是我家
...not my house.
这不是我家
It's not my house!
我家没有阳台
My house doesn't have balconies.
这就是你输入系统的地址  老兄
It's what you put in the system, mate.
不不不  没事  我  我很好
No, no, no. No, no, no. I'm-- I'm fine.
伙计  我要是留你一个人
Dude, if I leave you alone,
你该被自己的呕吐物呛死了
you're gonna choke on your own vomit.
-十分钟  就十分钟  -好吧
- Ten minutes, ten minutes. - Yeah, okay.
投资银行部怎么样  你今天走得挺早
How's IBD? You're out early.
我不知道  我觉得
Yeah, I don't know, I think...
我觉得他们针对我
I think they treat me differently.
比如说我上的是公立学校
Like I went to state school, and...
他们  他们跟我说话的方式都不一样
they-- they-- they even talk to me differently.
和我一桌的一个家伙  加斯
This guy on my desk, Gus,
我感觉他把工作当成了私事
I feel like he makes it his personal business...
试图让我觉得
trying to make me feel like
我没有价值什么的
I'm unworthy of it or something.
他听起来真是个混蛋
He sounds like a fucking asshole.
我和一个女人吃晚饭的时候
This weird thing happened at dinner
发生了一件怪事
with this woman.
一个客户
A client.
那不错啊  你已经开始和客户吃饭了
That's good. You're doing dinners with clients already.
是啊  我的部门经理  达莉娅
Yeah. Daria, my line manager,
突然间邀请了我
just invited me out of the blue.
晚餐进展得超级好
It went really well.
然后那个客户送我回家
And the-- the client, she gave me a ride home,
然后
and...
她好像
she sort of...
摸了我
touched me...
她是个女人  你知道吧
and she's a woman, you know?
但是  我也不知道  就是有点
But I don't know, it was still kind of...
奇怪
Weird.
我以为她喜欢我那个提议
I thought she bit on an idea,
但她好像暂时不打算和我签单子
but she won't want to deal with me now.
这不可能传到皮尔庞特  对吧
There's no way that it could get back to Pierpoint, right?
哈里
Hari?
有人知道今天是星期几吗
Does anybody know what day of the week it is?
瑞西  你会喜欢这个的
Rishi, you'll love this...
昨晚你们后来进展如何
So, how did the rest of the dinner go last night?
不错  挺好的
Yeah, it was fun.
你知道吗  我从没见过谁
You know, I've never actually seen someone
能成功保持妮可的注意
successfully hold Nicole's attention.
她出了名的难搞定
She's a notoriously hard nut to crack.
你后续跟进了吗
Have you followed up?
我不确定我现在就能给客户打电话
I'm not really sure I'm comfortable calling clients yet.
-我会发封邮箱的  -行
- I'll send an email. - Cool.
你休息了吗
You rested?
饥饿救星改时间了
HungerFix have changed the time.
他们明早九点来
They're in at nine tomorrow,
而且他们的首席运营官很自闭
and their COO is autistic.
不  我不是讽刺  她有自闭症
No, I'm not being snide, she has autism.
说实话  她也有点犯贱
And levelling with you, she's also a bit of a cunt.
这些都无关紧要
Those things are unrelated.
麻利点  加斯  模型做得怎么样了
Speed and clarity. Gus, how's the model?
我会在今晚前写好评论
I'll be done turning comments by tonight.
我们得在早上六点之前把书送去印刷
We need to get the book to the printers by 6:00 am.
别通宵  但告诉我你能完成任务
Don't stay up all night, but tell me that's doable.
我真喜欢你们俩
I like you two a lot.
你是罗伯特吧
Hi. Robert?
我注意到
Uh, I've noticed that, uh,
汇率和外汇部  以及其他团队
rates and FX and all the other teams
都提前开会了
start their meeting pre-open.
消费者投资组合服务的团队什么时候开会
When does the CPS one start?
每天时间都不一样
It-- it changes day to day.
埃里克不经常在  所以由克莱门特决定
Eric's not usually in it, so it's Clement's call.
那好  我希望以后改成七点开会
Well, urn, I'd like it to run from seven from now on,
明天开始
starting tomorrow.
你能帮我召集大家吗
Can you just round everyone up for me?
七点准
Seven on the dot.
七点开会  如果我有孩子的话
Seven? If I was a father,
我的早晨就全被毁了
that would seriously fuck with my morning.
有人想下班后去喝一杯吗
Anyone up for an after work bevvie?
周四晚提神醒脑一下
Thursday night sharpener?
-去放松吗  -嗯  你想去吗
- What, a few looseners? - Yeah, you fancy it?
-去减压  -是的
- What, to take the edge off? - Yeah.
不了兄弟  还有换身西装吧
No, mate. And get a new suit.
你看上去就像黑客帝国里的尼奥
You look like fucking Neo.
我在忙别的事
I am doing anything else.
那我能拽你去吧
Surely I can drag you out?
拽我辫子吗
By my braids?
还是下次吧
Maybe next time.
我猜我们是这里
I guess we're the only people
唯二喜欢享乐的人
that like to have fun around here.
那是毒品吗
Is that packet?
K粉  咱们今天吃点素的
K. We're going vegan tonight.
我明天需要很早起来
See, I gotta be up really early.
干脆别睡了
Only if we go to bed.
丹尼尔·菲利普斯
卢辛达·杨
哈里·达尔
奥古斯都·萨基
英国投资银行
评估总结  管理案例
执行概要
字体  新罗马字体  13号
收购机会
饥饿救星  项目建议书
预备事项  进一步审核及评估
你很棒
You're sound.
先是晚餐  之后是派对
There was dinner, and then a party
为那些还有精力的人准备的
for those people who had the energy.
我从未见过如此多饥渴的人
Well, I have never seen so many lusted-after people
可他们又毫无性感的魅力
who were so utterly charmless, and sexless.
没有魅力  没有性生活
They were without charm and sex.
克莱门特  我们听过了
Clement, we've heard this one.
接下来呢
I wanna hear the rest.
你说什么
Excuse me?
抱歉
Sorry, urn...
我脑子有点不清醒
Sorry, m-- my head's a blur.
你知道的  连续两晚都有要紧事
You know, when two big nights catch up with you?
你是负责招待谁的
And, uh, who were you entertaining?
哪一位客户
Which client?
抱歉
Urn, sorry...
饥饿救星  项目建议书
给我们买一个新手机
Get us a new phone?
哈里  你要和我去开会  不错
Hari? You're in the meeting with me. Well Done.
加斯  希望你不会介意
Gus, I hope you don't mind?
他应得的
Well deserved.
这次算你赢了
One-nil to you.
但你没有认真听我说  就只有一页
Yeah, but you're not listening to me. It's just one page.
我把那一页的字体搞错了
I fucked up the font on that one page.
你能不能重印一下
Can you just reprint it?
会议是在上午九点  你不用
The meetings at 9:00 am. You don't have--
瑞士风格  12号字体
Helvetica 12.
看起来太业余了
It looks fucking amateur!
看右边
看左边
看上面
怂包
没见过成年人脱裤子撒尿吗
Never seen a grown man drop his trouser at a urinal?
我在95年神户大地震时见过有人这么尿
I saw a guy do it during the Kobe earthquake, '95.
他的屁股蛋子像8岁小孩那样粉嫩
He had an arse like an eight-year-old boy.
人们似乎忘记了
You know, people seem to have forgotten
你越喜欢销售  你赚的越多
the more you enjoy sales, the more money you make.
但如果你要整晚不睡
But if you're gonna stay out all night,
熨烫自己的衬衫
iron the box lines out of your shirt.
你不是来修灯的
You're not here to fix the lights.
达莉娅说马隆默瑟公司的会议进展不错
Daria said the Mallon Mercer meet went well.
-把那些变现  -她发了邮件
- Monetize that shit. - She sent an email.
我们不躲在邮件背后
We don't hide behind emails.
拿起电话  让对方下单
Get on the phone and ask for the fucking order.
瑞西  你给我擦鞋吧
Rishi! Will you shine my shoes?
去你妈的
Fuck yourself, mate.
对  我真的不知道
Yeah, I really don't know.
这边走  通过那里
Come this way. Through there.
哈里的死是场突如其来的悲剧
Hari's death is an unexpected tragedy.
接下去的24小时
The next 24 hours
以及我们的应对措施将十分关键
and the way we respond to this are defining.
不要跟媒体交谈
Do not speak to the press.
我希望你们不要
I'd rather you didn't speak to
跟这个办公室以外的任何人谈及此事
anyone outside of the office.
现在
For now,
这是尊重他人的表现
this is about respect.
之后会有关于此事的调查
There will be an inquiry into the circumstances.
科林  你个大怂包
Colin, you big wanker.
我觉得这有道理  闭上眼
I think it makes sense to close your eyes
任其发生
and let it happen.
市场已经因政策而过度饱和了
Market seems maxed out by policy,
但真正想想改变方法的话  她...
but genuinely thinking of correction, she's...
我同意  我同意
I-- I agree, I agree.
他们叫规模压力  因为正在上调
They're called scale tension because they're pulling up.
饥饿救星的飞机取消了
Uh, HungerFix's flight got cancelled.
他们周一再来
They're in on Monday.
皮尔庞特公司
你...
Do you...
想谈谈吗
Want to talk about, you know?
安妮
你想出去吃饭吗  去个新餐厅
不了  之前很有趣  但你还是个孩子
调响点  哥们
Turn it up, mate.
陶德·巴巴
很守法啊你
如果你被抓了  我不存在
祝你好运
哈珀·斯登成绩单
纽约州立大学宾汉姆顿分校成绩单
哈珀·斯登
上传文件
上传中
你在干什么
What the fuck are you doing?
如果我听着很沮丧  那是因为我真的很沮丧
If I'm sounding frustrated, it's 'cause I am frustrated!
听说他就那么死了  倒地而亡
Apparently, he just fucking died. Like, collapsed.
-太吓人了  -教训是
- It's fucking scary. - Lesson is,
绝不雇佣那些真正需要这工作的人
don't hire people who really need the job.
这是什么意思
What does that mean?
有些人觉得他们需要
I mean, certain types of people feel the need
过度补偿  因为觉得自己不够好
to overcompensate, because they feel inadequate.
-对我们也不利  -什么意思
- It's also bad for us. - How do you mean?
就说那个戴鼻环的姑娘吧
Take the girl with the nose ring.
难道我们
Isn't it impossible
不都没法与她的天生种族特性比吗
to compete with this girl's narrative?
对她来说  一切都顺风顺水
I mean, everything's aligned for her.
你根本不了解她
You know nothing about her.
我知道她上了所烂大学
Well, I know she went to a shit uni,
还知道她是黑人
and I know she's black.
我知道这些事情并不互斥  当然
And I know those things are mutually exclusive, sure,
但合在一起  叮叮
but together... tick, tick.
-你太邪恶了  -得了吧
- You are fucking vile. - Oh, come on.
这不过是...现实
It's just... realistic.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry, uh...
我是那个不那么婊的
I was the less cunt y one.
没关系
It's fine.
反正那也不是正经的交易
It's not the correct trade anyway.
我什么时候让你站在错误的一方了
When do I ever have you on the wrong side of anything?
我知道  悲剧  好  晚点说
I know. Tragic. All right, catch you later.
-喂  -妮可
- Hello? - Nicole, hi,
我是皮尔庞特的哈珀
it's Harper from Pierpoint.
还记得我们谈的期权那事吗
That option idea we talked about?
那晚很有趣
It was a fun night.
买五亿
Let's go for it in half a yard.
瑞西  瑞西
Rishi? Rishi?
瑞西  我喊你名字了  哥们
Rishi, I said your fucking name, dude.
你能给我们之前谈的那个期权估价五亿吗
Can you price that option idea we talked about, half yard?
不可能  那比彩票的几率还小
No way. It's wingier than the fucking lottery.
再说你怎么能找到人买期权
And how the hell have you got someone to buy an option
这会国债收益率都到4%了
on treasury yields hitting four percent?
我跟她说  美国总有一天
I told her that eventually the US is going to war
会跟中国南海开战  到那时这个就赚翻了
in the South China Sea. When they do, this pays out.
好吧  能给她2.5个亿
All right. Can do it in half her amount.
妮可  2.5个亿可以吗
Nicole, can we do half?
不行  你想要我的单子
No. You want to write my business,
你想要我的第一份指示单
you fill me on my first order.
-就要五亿  -稍等
- In full. - Two secs.
-必须要五亿  你能帮忙吗  -绝对不行
- Need it in full, can you help? - No fucking way.
我这么估价肯定赔钱
I can't price it without losing money.
-那可是五亿啊  -客户不想听"不"
- That's half a billion. - The client will not hear "No,"
我也对那不感兴趣
and I'm not interested in that either.
五个基点
Offer is five beeps.
-五个基点  -太高了
- Offer is five basis points. - Too high.
2.5个亿我能给四个基点
I'll pay four cents in up to 250.
-其他你自己算  -五不行  只能四
- Work the balance with you. - Can't do five. Four, please.
如果他们愿意为你的主意买单  就让他们出钱
If they're paying for your idea, make them fucking pay.
四个基点
Four cents.
因为我厉害  四个基点给你了
Because I'm excellent, four cents.
我直接说"搞定"吗
Do I just say, "Done"?
"五亿搞定  四个基点"
"Half a yard done, four cents."
五亿搞定  四个基点
Half a yard done, four cents.
看看之后会如何
Let's see where this takes us.
别忘了你现在的感受
Do not forget how this feels right now.
你是个世界级杀手
You are a world killer.
-现在我看到你了  -谢谢
- Now I see you. - Thank you.
你鼻子上怎么有个环
Why is there a ring in your nose?
怎么  你是牛吗
What are you, cattle?
欢迎光临香格里拉酒店
Welcome to the Shangri-La Hotel.
能给我个今晚的房间吗  就今天一晚
Can I get a room for the night? Just the night.
我不想住家里
Somewhere else.
我们还有萨瑟克套房
We have the Southwark Suite.
就要那个
Let's do it.
上传文件
哈珀·斯登成绩单
上传中
文件上传完毕